UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials
1978-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Local 23-25
6000/024 AV
36 cubic feet
33.9 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
5751552
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 11, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/024: UNITE Local 23-25 Records 6000/024 P: UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/024 PUBS: UNITE Local 23-25 Publications 6000/024 MB: UNITE Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/050: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Files 6000/050 AV: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/050 MB: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/050 P: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/050 PUBS: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Publications
Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.) --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) -- Archives
5751552
- H and W rules part I, 1 (Box 5)
- June 1989 Union Voice - Romey on convention (Chinese), 2 (Box 5)
- Radio Program 1/25/1979, 3 (Box 5)
- English (all the labeling there was), 4 (Box 5)
- Price Seminar - 10/26/1979, 5 (Box 5)
- Seminar - GMT Price - Fir, Oct. 5, 1979, 6 (Box 5)
- B.A. Seminar, Oct. 11, 1979, 7 (Box 5)
- B.A. Seminar, Oct. 11, 1979, 8 (Box 5)
- Price Seminar, Sept. 28, 1979, 9 (Box 5)
- Grievance Board, Aug. 16, 1979, 10 (Box 5)
- Price Settlement Seminar, 9/21/1978, 11 (Box 5)
- Sept. 21, 1979, Price Settlement Seminar, 12 (Box 5)
- ILGWU - Local 23-25, Aired on 4/21 and 4/28/1984, 13 (Box 5)
- KQ/AMK, Re: Dragon Boat Festival Recipe - 6/2/1984; Alice and Connie - 6/9/1984, 14 (Box 5)
- Sweat Shops CNN Special Assignment - Kathy Slobogin, amos Gelb, Producer - Dec. 5, 1993, 15 (Box 5)
- Price Seminar, 10/3/1979, 16 (Box 5)
- Price Seminar - 10/26/1979, 17 (Box 5)
- Price Seminar - 10/3/1979, 18 (Box 5)
- Union Voice, 10/1985, 19 (Box 5)
- Union Voice, 9/1988 - Health Benefits, 20 (Box 5)
- 5/31 Show - Betty translation of E.R. Interview, 21 (Box 5)
- April 1989 Union Voice, 22 (Box 5)
- Union Voice - 6/1987, Immigration, Betty, May, Nancy, Judith, 23 (Box 5)
- Off Center, volume One, 1990, 24 (Box 5)
- Off Center, Fall 1991, 25 (Box 5)
- Off Center, Summer 1992, 26 (Box 5)
- Off Center, Summer 1992, 27 (Box 5)
- Off Center, Summer 1992, 28 (Box 5)
- Off Center, Fall 1993, 29 (Box 5)
- 12/1996, 30 (Box 5)
- 9/26/1989, Exec. Bd., 31 (Box 5)
- 6/23/1993, 32 (Box 5)
- 11/16/1983, 33 (Box 5)
- 11/1988, 34 (Box 5)
- Board Meeting, 9/20/1983, 35 (Box 5)
- Bd., 36 (Box 5)
- Kennedy Rally, 1 (Box 6)
  Scope and Contents
  CBS Television
- Sewing Woman by Arthur Dong, 1982; 2 (Box 6)
  1982, 16 mm
- Democracy is not a spectator sport, 3 (Box 6)
- New Member Filmstrip, 4 (Box 6)
  English
- New Member Filmstrip, 5 (Box 6)
- New Member Filmstrip, 6 (Box 6)
- New Member Filmstrip, 7 (Box 6)
- New Member Filmstrip, 8 (Box 6)
- New Member Filmstrip, 9 (Box 6)
- Vote Video, 1996; 10 (Box 6)
  10-12-1996 (compact VHS)
- New Members' Video 1990, 11 (Box 6)
  Chinese
- NYC Sweatshop/May Ying Chen, 1997; 12 (Box 6)
- New Members' Video 1990, 13 (Box 6)
  Spanish
- Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees, AFL-CIO,CLC, 14 (Box 6)
- Chinese - raw tape How to vote, 15 (Box 6)
- Summer School, Washington, vote machine, 16 (Box 6)
- Quitele la mascara, April 1991, 17 (Box 6)
- HP vs. Tektronix - Just the Facts, 18 (Box 6)
- New Members' Video 1990, 19 (Box 6)
- New Members' Video 1990, 20 (Box 6)
- New Members' Video 1990, 21 (Box 6)
- Stop Sweatshops!, 22 (Box 6)
- New Members' Video 1990, 23 (Box 6)
- How to vote, 24 (Box 6)
- Voices and Choices: Unmasking Job Discrimination, 25 (Box 6)
- New Members' Video 1990, 26 (Box 6)
- Clinton/Gore: The Man from Hope, 27 (Box 6)
- MLK, Jr. Center: Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. - I Have a Dream Speech, 28 (Box 6)
- Los Ninos Karatecas, 29 (Box 6)
- You Move, Your Pain, 30 (Box 6)
  Chinese version
- Local 23-25, ILGWU: New Members Video - Joining Hands, 31 (Box 6)
- Local 23-25, ILGWU: New Members Video - Joining Hands, 32 (Box 6)
  Spanish version
- NYAFL - 0101 -- Words, 2001; 33 (Box 6)
- Partners in Prevention: UNITE Safety and Health Committees in Action, 1 (Box 7)
- Made in the USA - 20/20 Friday, ABC-TV network, 1998; 2 (Box 7)
  March 13, 1998
- s in Prevention: UNITE Safety and Health Committees in Action, 3 (Box 7)
- UNITE: July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 4 (Box 7)
  English and Spanish
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 5 (Box 7)
- UNITE - How to Defend Your Rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite, 6 (Box 7)
- The Stereotyping of Chinese Americans and its Affect on US-China Relations, 2001; 7 (Box 7)
  Wednesday, March 7th, 2001
- UNITE for the future, 8 (Box 7)
- 1992 APALA Founding convention, 9 (Box 7)
- UNITE! A message from president Bruce Raynor, 10 (Box 7)
- Census 2000: A guide for Asian pacific Americans, 11 (Box 7)
  Cantonese
- Sweatshops Closed, 1997; 12 (Box 7)
- Through the eye of a needle, 13 (Box 7)
- Partners in prevention: UNITE Safety and Health Committees in Action, 14 (Box 7)
- UNITE! A message from president Bruce Raynor, 15 (Box 7)
- UNITE for the future, 16 (Box 7)
- UNITE: July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 17 (Box 7)
- Child Labor in the Airline Industry: UNITE!, 18 (Box 7)
- A Message from President Bruce Raynor, 19 (Box 7)
- NAFTA: Garment Factory by Hong Kong, 1992; 20 (Box 7)
- NHK Morning News - Jan. 4th, 2002: Made in NY, 21 (Box 7)
- Mightier than the sword, ILC 1990, 22 (Box 7)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 23 (Box 7)
  English/Spanish
- No pain, more gain: What the C.A.F. fund can do for you, 24 (Box 7)
- NAFTA: Garment Factory 1992 by Hong Zhang, 25 (Box 7)
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 26 (Box 7)
- Is There a Sweatshop in Your Future?, 27 (Box 7)
- Global Fairness Lobby Day - 4/4/2000, 28 (Box 7)
  Prep video
- Partners in Prevention: UNITE Safety and Health Committees in Action, 29 (Box 7)
- Leaving Home - short version, 30 (Box 7)
- The Shame of Saipan: 20/20 ABC Network, 31 (Box 7)
- Sweatshop Protest - Chinatown, 32 (Box 7)
- Partners in prevention: UNITE Safety and Health Committees in Action, 33 (Box 7)
- Good Day New York (WNYW, Ch. 5): 3 part segment on Sweatshops, 34 (Box 7)
- Restoring employee rights is good for America, 35 (Box 7)
- New Members Video 1990, 36 (Box 7)
- UNITE: Day Care/Good Day NY / FOX 5; UNITE: Washington Trip/ FOX 5, 37 (Box 7)
- NAFTA-Eye Witness, 38 (Box 7)
- Zoned for Slavery, 39 (Box 7)
- Asian Pacific American labor Alliance Convention and Aston Hotel Protest, 2001; 40 (Box 7)
  TV News Coverage: Wed. 8/15/2001-Sat. 8/18/2001
- UNITE: Airline Linen - Electronic Coverage - 11/20-27/2000, 41 (Box 7)
- Our Story: a musical by local 23-25, ILGWU, 42 (Box 7)
- ACTWU #2 -- 6/28/1995, 1 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - Day 3; tape 7 -- 6/26/1995, 2 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - #2 -- 6/23/1995, 3 (Box 8)
- ILGWU #2 -- 6/23/1995, 4 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - Day 2 #5 -- 6/24/1995, 5 (Box 8)
- We are one, 6 (Box 8)
- We are one, 7 (Box 8)
- We are one (Chinese Version), 8 (Box 8)
- We are one - MASTER, 9 (Box 8)
- Local 23-25, ILGWU-AFL-CIO -- Chinese MASTER, 1983; 10 (Box 8)
  1983
- The Employer Guide to Understanding IRCA: Fair Employment Provisions, 1 (Box 9)
  English, Cantonese, Mandarin
- Restoring Employee Rights is Good for America, 2 (Box 9)
- 1990 Chinese New Year, 3 (Box 9)
- Leaving Home - Short Version: We do the work, 4 (Box 9)
- Super Sewers Cycle, 5 (Box 9)
- Adult education week: ILGWU worker family education program. - 11/20/1987, 6 (Box 9)
- It's all about jobs, 7 (Box 9)
- UNITE! - Because every vote counts, 8 (Box 9)
- Domestic violence: Unions Respond, 9 (Box 9)
- $4 a day? No WAY! - Joining Hands Across the Border, 10 (Box 9)
- GIDC Graduation - 12/21/1989, 11 (Box 9)
- CLUW: The Power of Sisterhood, 12 (Box 9)
- The Man from hope: Clinton/Gore, 13 (Box 9)
- UNITE! - Porque su voto hace, la diferencia, 14 (Box 9)
- How legal immigrants strengthen America, 1996; 15 (Box 9)
- What happened to the American dream?, 16 (Box 9)
- Organizing - the Job that changes lives, 17 (Box 9)
- Chinatown is vulnerable too - NYU/Journalism, 18 (Box 9)
- Local 23-25 Chinatown New Years - Celebration - Sunday March 1, 1987, 19 (Box 9)
- NAFTA, 20 (Box 9)
- Sino vision, 21 (Box 9)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 22 (Box 9)
- ILGWU: UNITE and Fight, 23 (Box 9)
- We do the work: Sewing our future, 24 (Box 9)
- TVG: Silent Danger, 25 (Box 9)
  Chinese Version
- Silent Danger, 26 (Box 9)
- Leslie Fay: We don't buy it, 1994; 27 (Box 9)
- Silent Danger, 28 (Box 9)
- Leslie Fay: we don't buy it, 29 (Box 9)
- Caring for your newborn, 30 (Box 9)
  Mandarin version
- Local 23-25, ILGWU, Celebrating the Chinese New Year, Sunday, March 3, 1991, 31 (Box 9)
- Muzzafar Chishti, Allan Wernick - Tape 1, 1 (Box 10)
- Allan Wernick; Mike Hogan - Tape 2 -- 4/21/1987, 2 (Box 10)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 3 (Box 10)
- Dave Malask(?) Interview, part I, 4 (Box 10)
- There's still time, 1996; 5 (Box 10)
- KDKA Coverage and outtakes - Caliguri Dedication, 6 (Box 10)
- With these hands, 7 (Box 10)
- Raise the minimum wage!: A populist issue for the Democratic Party, 2000; 8 (Box 10)
- Wilbur Daniels - Welcome - Reactions, 9 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Immi Seminar - Tape 3 - 4/22/1987, 10 (Box 10)
- Yeakel-Specter, 11 (Box 10)
- Surviving the bottom line with Hendrick Smith, 12 (Box 10)
- UNITE: G"UESS who pockets the difference?, 13 (Box 10)
  part 1-English; part 2-Spanish
- CBC Newsworld - Rough Cuts - The Suit War, 1997; 14 (Box 10)
  aired March 10, 1997
- ILGWU Immigrant Seminar - 4/22/1987 - Tape I, 15 (Box 10)
- ILGWU- Immigration Seminar - Tape 2 - 4/22/1987, 16 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Immigration Seminar - Chishti Stansbury - 4/23/1987 - Tape 1, 17 (Box 10)
- UNITE! Because every vote counts, 18 (Box 10)
- The True Cost of NAFTA: a report from the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 19 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Immigration Seminar - Tape 2 - 4/23/1987, 20 (Box 10)
- Stop Sweatshops! The video, 21 (Box 10)
- UNITE! Stop Sweatshops Campaign, December, 1996, 22 (Box 10)
- Intracorp Smart Choices, 1995; 23 (Box 10)
- No grapes, 24 (Box 10)
- Newman for Supreme Court - Person to Person, 25 (Box 10)
- Fechheimer Uniforms: the truth behind the labels, 26 (Box 10)
- Sweat Shops CNN Special Assignment: Kathy Slobogin, Dec. 5, 1993, 27 (Box 10)
- NY is Fashion: ILGWU - Ruth Glanz Productions, August, 1992, 28 (Box 10)
- Senate Hearings on Undocumented Workers, 29 (Box 10)
- Labor Immigrant Assistance Project -, 30 (Box 10)
  PSA #1: Grounds of Exclusion; PSA #2: Have no fear
- DATELINE - 12/17/1996 - Toy Story, 31 (Box 10)
- Facts on File - 6/16/1987, 32 (Box 10)
- Facts on file - 6/16/1987, 33 (Box 10)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 1 (Box 11)
- UNITE! - Members love New York, 2 (Box 11)
- UNITE - Oceanside Workers Strike -, 2000; 3 (Box 11)
- UNITE! Tape - June 1995, 4 (Box 11)
- Global Fairness Lobby Day 4/4/2000, 5 (Box 11)
- Unite New Members, 6 (Box 11)
  English; Spanish
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 7 (Box 11)
- Stop Sweatshops!, 8 (Box 11)
- Stop Sweatshops!, 9 (Box 11)
- Global Fairness Lobby Day 4/4/2000, 10 (Box 11)
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 11 (Box 11)
- Stop Sweatshops! The video, 12 (Box 11)
- Chinatown Manpower Project Workplace Literacy Program, 13 (Box 11)
  Garment-Related Bilingual TV Broadcast Lessons (episode 9 to 15)
- Global Fairness Lobby Day 4/4/2000, 14 (Box 11)
- Global Assembly Line, 15 (Box 11)
- UNITE: GUESS who pockets the difference?, 16 (Box 11)
  Part 1-English; Part 2 Spanish
- Everyday heroes, 17 (Box 11)
- Unlabeled, 18 (Box 11)
- Title is written in Chinese on tape, 19 (Box 11)
- UNITE for the future, 20 (Box 11)
- Unite New Members, 21 (Box 11)
- Merger Convention Highlights - 2004, 22 (Box 11)
- 1987 Labor Day Parade, 23 (Box 11)
  Promotional Video
- Unlabeled, 24 (Box 11)
- Unlabeled, 25 (Box 11)
- ILGWU Presents: The Sweatshop - Homework Menace, 1981; 26 (Box 11)
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day against sweatshops, 27 (Box 11)
- UNITE: Campaign for the future, 28 (Box 11)
- UNITE: Campaign for the future, 29 (Box 11)
  English version
- Looking back moving forward, 30 (Box 11)
- Caring for your newborn, 31 (Box 11)
  Cantonese version
- 12/1 ESL, 32 (Box 11)
- The Golden Door by Michael Fried, 33 (Box 11)
- Local 23-25 ILGWU: New Members Video: Joining Hands, 34 (Box 11)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 1 (Box 12)
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 2 (Box 12)
- UNITE - How to defend your rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite, 3 (Box 12)
- Title is written in Chinese, 4 (Box 12)
- Unlabeled, 5 (Box 12)
- UNITE! A message from president Bruce Raynor - 12/6/2001, 6 (Box 12)
- UNITE How to defend your rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite, 7 (Box 12)
- Union Summer, 8 (Box 12)
- Saving Social Security, 9 (Box 12)
- Daycare video - 7/29/1999, 10 (Box 12)
- Chinatown manpower project workplace literacy program, 11 (Box 12)
  Garment - related bilingual TV broadcast lessons - episode 1 to 8
- UNITE - How to defend your rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite, 12 (Box 12)
- The GAP in Guatemala: behind the gates of Shin Won, 13 (Box 12)
- UNITE - How to defend your rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite, 14 (Box 12)
- At the river I stand, 15 (Box 12)
- No pain, more gain, 16 (Box 12)
- A message from President Bruce Raynor, 17 (Box 12)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 18 (Box 12)
- We do the work: Show 309: Sewing our future, 19 (Box 12)
- Chinatown manpower project workplace literacy program, 20 (Box 12)
  Garment-related bilingual TV broadcast lessons - Episode 1 to 8
- The Greater Blouse Association Presents - Made in New York, 21 (Box 12)
- September 11th Fund: Taking your life back, 22 (Box 12)
- UNITE for a real union, 23 (Box 12)
- UNITE for a real union, 24 (Box 12)
- ILGWU Union Label Ads, 25 (Box 12)
  tape #164
- Local 23-25 ILGWU: New Members Video - Joining Hands, 26 (Box 12)
  Chinese video
- Tahari: the changing fabric of NY Real Estate, 27 (Box 12)
- Leslie Fay: We don't buy it, 1994; 28 (Box 12)
- UNITE Immigration Project: Count me in: a Bridge to Citizenship, 29 (Box 12)
- Local 23-25 ILGWU: New Members Video - Joining Hands, 30 (Box 12)
- Your move, your pain, 31 (Box 12)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union: Its about jobs, 32 (Box 12)
- Local 23-25 ILGWU - New members video - Joining Hands, 33 (Box 12)
- UNITE! Because every vote counts, 1 (Box 13)
- UNITE! Because every vote counts, 2 (Box 13)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 3 (Box 13)
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 4 (Box 13)
- Energy and you, 5 (Box 13)
- Proceedings of the Ad Hoc democratic Party Platform Hearings, 2000; 6 (Box 13)
- New York State AFL-CIO: 1997 Voter guide for the Constitutional Convention, 7 (Box 13)
- Unite New Members, 8 (Box 13)
  English, Spanish
- UNITE! - Porque su voto hace la diferencia, 9 (Box 13)
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 10 (Box 13)
- The Battle for Medicare / National Council of Senior Citizens, 1995; 11 (Box 13)
- Welcome to the Chase Customer Assistance Team, 12 (Box 13)
- 2001 Labor Day Parade, 13 (Box 13)
- Day Care Center, 14 (Box 13)
- Unlabeled, 15 (Box 13)
- Unlabeled, 16 (Box 13)
- Unlabeled, 17 (Box 13)
- Unite New Members, 18 (Box 13)
- Collette Tours: Spain and Portugal, 19 (Box 13)
- Alaska on the windward, 20 (Box 13)
- Clinton/Gore: The Man from hope, 21 (Box 13)
- Zoned for slavery, 22 (Box 13)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 23 (Box 13)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 24 (Box 13)
- Global Fairness Lobby Day 4/4/2000, 25 (Box 13)
- UNITE for the future, 26 (Box 13)
- Assemblyman Dave Townsend: Debate on Assembly Bill 10250-A, March 30, 2000, 27 (Box 13)
- UNITE! Because every vote counts, 28 (Box 13)
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops, 29 (Box 13)
- An Inspiration vacation, 30 (Box 13)
- UNITE! Because every vote counts, 31 (Box 13)
- Unlabeled, 32 (Box 13)
- UNITE for the future, 33 (Box 13)
- UNITE for the future, 34 (Box 13)
- WW II - Ships, Planes, Flames, 1 (Box 14)
  CAM MASTER
- ILGWU - 6/23/1995 #1, 2 (Box 14)
- ILGWU - 6/24/1995 Day 2, 3 (Box 14)
- ACTWU - 6/28/1995 #5, 4 (Box 14)
- ILGWU - 6/26/1995 - #9 - Day 3, 5 (Box 14)
- ILGWU - Day 3, Tape 8 - 6/26/1995, 6 (Box 14)
- Everyday Heroes, 7 (Box 14)
- Partners in prevention: UNITE Safety and Health, Committees in Action, 8 (Box 14)
- Organized Labor, March 10, 1996, 9 (Box 14)
  CBS Sunday Morning
- People get ready: UNITE Southern Region 1997, 10 (Box 14)
- UNITE Ads, 11 (Box 14)
- UNITE; Words; Face, 12 (Box 14)
- Amity Workers - UNITE for respect, 13 (Box 14)
- UNITE: GUESS who pockets the difference, 14 (Box 14)
  part 1 - English; part 2 Spanish
- Dateline - 12/17/1996; Toy Story, 15 (Box 14)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 16 (Box 14)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 17 (Box 14)
- The Heart knows better by Ken Kimmelman, 18 (Box 14)
  Imagery Film, Ltd.
- Maramount Corporation - 9 News - 8/22/1994, 1 (Box 16)
- No pain, More gain: What the C.A.F. fund can do for you, 2 (Box 16)
- Partners in prevention: UNITE Safety and Health Committees in Action, 3 (Box 16)
- Hard Copy, three part series on Nicaraguan sweatshops, 1997; 4 (Box 16)
  November 1997
- UNITE: How to defend your rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite, 5 (Box 16)
- The Employee Guide to Understanding IRCA, Fair Employment Provisions, 6 (Box 16)
- Leslie Fay Strike, 1994; 7 (Box 16)
  6/1994
- We are one, 8 (Box 16)
- Future Shop: A modular manufacturing shop, 9 (Box 16)
- ILGWU: Count me in - a bridge to Citizenship (short version), 9/23/1994, 10 (Box 16)
- ILGWU Immigration Project - Count me in a bridge to citizenship (long version), 9/11/1995, 11 (Box 16)
- We do the work - Sewing our future, 12 (Box 16)
- Work in America Institute, Parent Connection, Overview and parent testimonials, 13 (Box 16)
- Mouseland, 14 (Box 16)
- Strengthen Social Security, 15 (Box 16)
- No Grapes, 16 (Box 16)
- Unlabeled, 17 (Box 16)
- Leading edge information to help you Live Better with Arthritis, 18 (Box 16)
- The Crisis in America's Health Care System, 19 (Box 16)
- Cruising the world with Marco Polo, 20 (Box 16)
- Local 23-25 ILGWU - New Members Video, Joining Hands, 21 (Box 16)
- Portugal, 22 (Box 16)
- NLRB and Supreme Court, 1 (Box 17)
- Union Voice - 12/1997, 1 (Box 18)
- Union Voice - 3/1988, 1 (Box 19)
- Union Voice - Sept. 1986, 1 (Box 20)
- Interview with Stanley L. - Wages, Holidays, Day Care Center, Immigration/Chinese New Year Celebration, 1984; 1 (Box 21)
- Union Voice 1/1990, 1 (Box 22)
- Union Voice, March 1987, 1 (Box 23)
- Q and A with Horris Zinn, Union Voice, 1/25/1988, 1 (Box 24)
- Union Voice - May 1990, 1 (Box 25)
- Union Voice - Interview with Edgar Romney - 1/6/1986, 1 (Box 26)
- Union Voice, Local 2325 - 12/29/1984, 1 (Box 27)
- Radio Show 3/1989 and 8/1989, 1 (Box 28)
- Union Voice - 6/4/1983 and 6/11/1983, 1 (Box 29)
- Union Voice 2/1997, 1 (Box 30)
- Sam and Sabrina, re: Mondale vs. Reagan - 10/27, 1 (Box 31)
- Union Voice - 12/1992, 1 (Box 32)
- Union Voice - April 1990, 1 (Box 33)
- Union Voice - 3/1997, 6/1997, 1 (Box 34)
- Union Voice - April 1988; Q and A with Edgar Rommy, 1 (Box 35)
- Union Voice - 11/1990, 1 (Box 36)
- New Years Message by Edgar Rommy, Union Voice 1/1988, 1 (Box 37)
- Dec. 1993 (Union Voice?), 1 (Box 38)
- Interview with Rommy, air date: 6/14/1985, 1 (Box 39)
- YMCA Day Camp - 6/21/1984, 1 (Box 40)
- Union Voice - Nov. 1989, 1 (Box 41)
- Interview with Stanley L - Holiday pay rules, 1/7/1984; How the Holiday fund works, 1/14/1984, 1 (Box 42)
- Union Voice, 10/1987, 1 (Box 43)
- Betty w/Cindy Chow, re: Nutrition for Seniors - 4/7/1984, 1 (Box 44)
- Union Voice - 9/1990, 1 (Box 45)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 46)
- Show: Interview with E.R., re: contract negotiations -- 5/31/1985, 1 (Box 47)
- Union Voice - July 1996, 1 (Box 48)
- Sam's translation of E.R. interview re: non-pay, 1 (Box 49)
- Union Voice - MAP 11/1987, 1 (Box 50)
- Union Voice - 7/1993, 1 (Box 51)
- Union Voice - 7/1990, 1 (Box 52)
- Ex Bd. 7/28/1988, 1 (Box 53)
- Ex.Bd. - 3/12/1985, 1 (Box 54)
- 4/27/1987, 1 (Box 55)
- 5/16, 1 (Box 56)
- Shop Rep Seminar - 2/27/1982, 1 (Box 57)
- UAG Ex -- 12/11/1985, 1 (Box 58)
- Ex. Bd. - 3/20, 1 (Box 59)
- GM Meeting - 3/27/1985, 1 (Box 60)
- Shop Report Ex. Bd. Meeting -7/27/1993, 1 (Box 61)
- Ex. Bd. - 8/20/1985, 1 (Box 62)
- Ex. Bd. - 7/19/1989, 1 (Box 63)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 64)
- Nov. 26, 1984, 1 (Box 65)
- Ex. Bd. - 10/30/1984, 1 (Box 66)
- Ex. Bd. Meeting - Dec. 18, 1 (Box 67)
- 3/22/1983, 1 (Box 68)
- Board Meeting - 1/12/1985, 1 (Box 69)
- Ex. Bd. - 10/19/1983, 1 (Box 70)
- 9/20/1984, 1 (Box 71)
- Ex. Bd. - 7/30/1987, 1 (Box 72)
- Ex. Bd. - 2/6/1988, 1 (Box 73)
- Shop Rep - 5/29/1985 - Meeting, 1 (Box 74)
- Ex. Bd. Meeting, 1 (Box 75)
- 11/23/1993, 1 (Box 76)
- Oct. 29, 1 (Box 77)
- Board - 1/25/1983, 1 (Box 78)
- 12/21/1983, 1 (Box 79)
- Ex. Bd. - 10/30, 1 (Box 80)
- 5/16, 1 (Box 81)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 82)
- 6/15, 1 (Box 83)
- 5/23/1985, 1 (Box 84)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 85)
- 1986 Election, 1 (Box 86)
- Oct. 1984, 1 (Box 87)
- Press - 6/5/1985, 1 (Box 88)
- Conference, 1 (Box 89)
- Shop Rep - 11/23/1983, 1 (Box 90)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 91)
- 7/17/1984, 1 (Box 92)
- Board - 3/1/1983, 1 (Box 93)
- 7/17/1984, 1 (Box 94)
- 1/23/1985, 1 (Box 95)
- Board meeting - Oct. 19, 1 (Box 96)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 97)
- Ex. Bd. - 1/23/1986, 1 (Box 98)
- Election 1982, 7 (Box 99)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 100)
- Ex. Bd. - 4/24/1985, 1 (Box 101)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 102)
- Board - 12/14/1982, 1 (Box 103)
- Camy - Lion Rock IV and V, 1 (Box 104)
- 8/1986, 1 (Box 105)
- Ex. Bd. - 5/11/1985, 1 (Box 106)
- 3/26/1985, 1 (Box 107)
- 10/17/1985, 1 (Box 108)
- Election, UAG - Dec 2, 1985, 1 (Box 109)
- Shop Rep, 1 (Box 110)
- 5/21/1986 - Ex. Bd., 1 (Box 111)
- Press Conference - Feb. 14, 1 (Box 112)
- Press Conference - 3/27/1985, 1 (Box 113)
- Ex. Bd. - 9/23/1986, 1 (Box 114)
- Book - 8/19/1983, 1 (Box 115)
- 3/20/1984, 1 (Box 116)
- Union Voice - 7/1989, 1 (Box 117)
- 23-25 -- 11/1/1985, 1 (Box 118)
- WEVD Local 2325 - Chinese Broadcast - 12/22/1984, 1 (Box 119)
- 5/16 Show - Katie and Garment Workers - re: defend contract committee, 1 (Box 120)
- Union Voice - 8/1987, 1 (Box 121)
- Katie and May - re: Labor Fair, 1 (Box 122)
- Union Voice - July 1988, 1 (Box 123)
- ILGWU 23-25 Shows 3 and 4 - 5/21 and 5/28, 1 (Box 124)
- 4/19, 1 (Box 125)
- Nov. 20, 1 (Box 126)
- Nov. 20, 1 (Box 127)
- 1988 Contract negotiation - 3/19/1988, 1 (Box 128)
- Betty with Jay and Edgar - 7/9 /1983, 1 (Box 129)
- Local 23-25 - Show #1-5/7/1983; Show #2-5/14/1983, 1 (Box 130)
- Union Voice - 5/1988, 1 (Box 131)
- 2/1988 - Chinatown Radio Shows, 1 (Box 132)
- ILGWU - Local 12325 - WEVD Broadcast - 3/17/1984, 1 (Box 133)
- Union Voice - April 1987, 1 (Box 134)
- Union Voice - 10/1987, 1 (Box 135)
- 23-25 -- 10/4/1985, 1 (Box 136)
- Off Center - Spring 1993, 1 (Box 137)
- Chinatown Manpower Project, Inc. Workplace Literacy Program, 1 (Box 138)
  English and Chinese Garment-Related Broadcast